So many of you were asking which
tint do you use, which is literally finished now
and trust me this is my fourth
or fifth bottle which I have restocked again. It is the
tint, its name is Tude Water
Tint, this is the double of Bene Tint, it is more
expensive and to be honest I have
heard better reviews of it than this.
This is how it looks like this, if you
want its link then let me know. I will
tell you its benefits, you look
so fresh at once when you apply it. Second and the
most important thing is that you apply it in the morning
and literally it stays till evening, it seems there is
no drawback also, if you
apply it and leave it, if you do like this, apply it
here, apply it here, apply it
here, blend it later, by then
it gets set, so
you have to blend it as soon as you apply it,
on your eyes, cheeks, nose, everywhere it is the tint
that I use every day and I love it